Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine subject files and photographs, 1888-2004
24-4-3385
32.2 cubic ft.2 oversize folders.
Correspondence, Manuscripts, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection contains materials relating to the history and founding of the College, administration and various departments including academics, the clinic, and buildings.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine was founded in 1894. It was originally named the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection contains materials relating to the history and founding of the College, administration and various departments including academics, the clinic, and buildings. Included are reports, notes, files, course materials, evaluations, handbooks, building plans, calendars, schedules, newspaper clippings, flyers, sketches, posters, photographs, rosters, sketches, directories, programs, postcards, photographs, slides, films, and guest books.
Also includes faculty biographical files.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine.; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine--Administration.; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine--Students.; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine--Alumni and alumnae.
Subjects:
Veterinary medicine--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Veterinary medicine--Study and teaching.
Form and Genre Terms:
Building plans.; Calendars.; Directories.; Film clips.; Flyers (printed matter).; Photographs.; Picture postcards.; Posters.; Programs.; Rosters; Schedules (time plans).; Sketches.; Slides (photographs).; Visitors' books.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
See also the Veterinary College of Medicine Biomedical Communications Dept. records, #24-14-3352 and the Veterinary College of Medicine Dept. of Communications records, #24-10-3338.
SERIES LIST
Series I. History and Founding
Series II. Academic Miscellaneous
Series III. Administrative Miscellaneous
Series IV. Alumni and Students
Photographs and Slides
Series V. Buildings and Facilities
Photographs
Series VI. Calenders and Schedules
Series VII. Committees and Boards
Series VIII. Departments, Units, and Services
Photographs and Slides
Series IX. Events and classes
Photographs and Slides
Series X. Faculty and Staff
Biographical Files (including photographs)
Millennium Video Project Interviews
Faculty Portraits
Series XI. Offices and Functions
Series XII. Programs and Conferences
Series XIII. Graphics and Audiovisual Material
Series XIV. Miscellaneous
Photographs and Slides
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. History and Founding
  - Founding of the College (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Histories of the College (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Copy of James Law's Last Will and Testament, 1921; Slides of Buildings and Labs from 1800s-1900s, 1800s-1921 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Legacy of Women in Veterinary Medicine - printout of website, copy of Dean Donald Smith's Keynote Address, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Series II. Academic Miscellaneous
  - General (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Scholarships (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Short Course for Veterinarians, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Senior Seminars-Guidelines, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Senior Seminars-Clinical Reports, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Senior Seminars-Clinical Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Six Years Course for Dual Degree DVM/MD, 1890's (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Class Notes
    - Leo Wuori's notes - Anatomy, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Leo Wuori's notes - Blood and Urine Analysis, 1938-1942 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Leo Wuori's notes - Dairy I (pre-vet), 1938 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Leo Wuori's notes - Ophthalmology, 1938-1942 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Leo Wuori's notes - General Surgery w/ A.G. Danks, 1938-1942 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Zimmerman's Files, 1931-1935 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Exams
    - Anatomy, 1917-1947 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Animal Husbandry, 1926-1938 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Bacteriology, 1897-1947 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Pathogenic Bacteriology, 1927-1937 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Chemistry, 1925-1935, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Embryology, 1926-1934 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - English, 1931-1934 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Histology, 1924-1936 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Infectious Diseases, 1929-1931, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Small Animal Diseases and Large Animal Diseases, 1927-1950 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Meat and Dairy Inspection, 1897-1923 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Dairy Industry, 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Materia Medica and Pharmacology, 1925-1937 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Medicine, 1926-1934 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Military Department, Veterinary Unit, 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Parasitology, 1924-1931 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - General Pathology, 1897-1924, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Special Pathology, 1910-1916 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Pathology of Infectious Diseases, 1900-1922 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Physiology, 1918-1945 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Poultry Diseases, 1931-1939 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Infectious Diseases (W.A. Hagan), 1933 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Surgery, 1926-1947 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Veterinary Science 120 and Surgical Anatomy, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous, 1900-1915, 1927-1932, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Exams and Notes - Vertebrate Zoology, 1932-1935 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Course Syllabi
    - Pathology, 1896-1915 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Parasitology, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Food Hygeine, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Genetic Reproduction, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous A-D, 1955-1958 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Experimental Physiology, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Experimental Physiology, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous F-W, 1955-1958 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Clinical Pathology Conference, 1964-1970 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Information About the Collection of Syllabi from the 190s and 1970s, 1971, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Avian Diseases 255 and 557, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Pathogenic Microbiology 340, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Microbiology 515-517, 519, 705, 706, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Physiology - General, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Physiology 526 and 527, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Pharmacology 528 and Toxicology 621, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Anatomy 500-506, 700, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Anatomy 500 - Gross Anatomy, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Anatomy 501, 503-506, 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Anatomy 507, 508, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Pathology 535-537, 571, 740, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Veterinary Pathology, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Large animal Medicine, Obstetrics and Surgery 561-566, 683, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Clinical Courses 568, 569, 571-578, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Small Animal Medicine 586-584, folder 1, 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Small Animal Medicine 586-584, folder 2, 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Small Animal Surgery 585-587, 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Small Animal Ophthalmology 588, 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Physiology 611 and 612, 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Special Pathology 632, 1970-1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Animal Parasitology 635, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Bacteriology and Immunology 641, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Food Quality Control 730, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Applied Parasitology 731, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Veterinary Medicine 740 - Epidemiological Methods, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Diseases of Poultry, 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Physical Biology 920 - Elements of Physical Biology, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Physical Biology 921, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Physical Biology 922 - Biological Effects of Radiation, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Physical Biology 923 - Biological Membranes and Nutrient Transfer, Robert Wasserman, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Physical Biology 924 - Functional Organization of the Nervous System, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Other Divisions - Mostly Animal Science, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - "Core Course Syllabi for the New Curriculum", 1972-12 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Elective Course, Folder 1, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Elective Course, Folder 2, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Core Courses 500-516, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Core Courses 517-526, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Core Courses 527-626, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Veterinary Mycology 516, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Veterinary Virology and Viral Diseases 517, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Class of 1997 Learning Objectives, 1993 (Box 14)
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: Neck, Abscesses-Tumors
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Small Animal Surgery: Head, Neck, Trunk, and Genital Organs and Extremities
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: HEAD, Fractures-Wounds
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: EXTREMITIES, Open Joint-Tendonitis
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: EXTREMITIES, Abcesses-Navicular Diseases
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: EXTREMITIES, Tendo-Vaginitis Wounds
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: Trunk and Genital Organs Fractures-Wounds
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: Trunk and Genital Organs Abscesses-Fistulous Withers
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: HEAD, Abscesses-Floating Teeth
  - Department of Pathology and Bacteriology (Box 20)
    Clinical Notes
  - Publishing Notes for animal diseases and ailments (Box 22)
- Series III. Administrative Miscellaneous
  - American Veterinary Medical Association Evaluation Report, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association Evaluation, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Budget Requests-State College Council, 1933-1937 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Budget Requests, 1959-1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Master Plan, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Master Plan, 1973-1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - N.Y.S. Senate Evaluation of the College, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Self Study Report to American Veterinary Medical Association, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Series IV. Alumni and Students
  - Alumni Association (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Lists (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Graduate Students (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Organizations
    - Alpha Psi (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Omega Tau Sigma (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Phi Zeta (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Society of Comparative Medicine, 1904-1908 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Society of Comparative Medicine, 1909-1916 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - SCAVMA/JAVMA - General, 1939-1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - SCAVMA/JAVMA - General, 1963-1965, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - SCAVMA/JAVMA - Minutes, 1947-1954 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - SCAVMA/JAVMA - Newsletters (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - SCAVMA/JAVMA - Directories (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - SCAVMA/JAVMA - Dues and Attendance Records, 1960s (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Student Handbooks, 1952-1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Student Handbooks, 1993,1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - "Measures" Unofficial News Bulletin of the Students of the NYS VC, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Organizations (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Graduate Students - Lists, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Class files, 1897-1933 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Class files, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Class files, 1935-1939 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Class files, 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Class files, 1942 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Contains V-9018
  - Class files, 1943-1949 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Class files, 1950-1959 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Class files (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Contains some negatives
  - Class files, 1970-1975 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Class files, 1976-1979 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Class files, 1980-1985 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Class files, 1986-1989 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Class files, 1990-1996 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Class files, 2000-2005 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Photographs and Slides
  - Accreditation Site Visit, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Association, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Association Dinner and Luncheon, 1990 and 1997 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Students in Company C, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Graduates - slides, 1995-1997 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Students, 1990s-2000 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Students in Clinics and Labs, 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Students in Classrooms - slides, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Students (slides), 1998-2000 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Tutorial Sessions, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Omega Tau Sigma composites and class photographs, 1920-1984 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Alpha Psi composites and class photographs, 1923-1931, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Gamma Alpha composites and class photographs, with class information, 1916-1923 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Class composites, 1900-2013 (Box 44)
- Series V. Buildings and Facilities
  - General (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Lower Campus - General (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1900 Fire-Histology Department Losses (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Upper Campus-General (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Upper Campus-Group III Equipment Estimates-F1, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Upper Camps-Group III Equipment Estimates-F2, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Upper Camps-Group III Equipment Estimates-F3, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Upper Campus-Group III Equipment Estimates-F4, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Upper Campus-Group IV Equipment Estimates, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Upper Campus-Space Requirements, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Research Tower, General (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Research Tower-Ulrich Franzen and Associated Material, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Research Tower-Earl L. Walls Associates Material, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Research Tower-Dedication, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Physical Biology Computer Facility-Proposal, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Veterinary Medical Center (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Facility Master Plan by Davis, Brody and Associates-Folder 1, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Facility Master Plan by Davis, Brody and Associates-Folder 2, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Space Allocation by Department, Davis, Brody etc., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Building Plans (Box 9)
  - Photographs
  - Aerial Views of Buildings - slides, 1959-1990s (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Various Buildings - slides, 1903-2002 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Various Buildings - some slides, 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Computer Labs, no date (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Learning Lab, 1990s (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Facilities Off Campus - slides, 1983-2003 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Labs - some slides, 1974-2001 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Lunging Arena, no date (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Modular Resource Center - slides, 1990s-2002 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Mouse House Dedication, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Muenscher Poisonous Plant Garden - slides, 1990s (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Research Tower, 1970s (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Research Tower Fire - slides, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Veterinary Medical Center Dedication, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Veterinary Medical Center Dedication - Design and Planning, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Vet College Photography, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Wet Lab, 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Aerial view of James Law Hall, Moore Lab, etc. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Clinic buildings and James Law Hall (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Clinic buildings in James Law Hall (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Architect's sketch of Moore Laboratory Building (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Front of Moore Laboratory with 4 cars (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - View of museum floor with display cases in James Law Hall (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Empty pathology and bacteriology laboratory -- in James Law Hall; no students (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Empty pathology and bacteriology laboratory -- in James Law Hall with a fume hood in the ceiling; no students (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Diagram of library stack level in Schurman Hall, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Sketch of Veterinary Research Tower, 2000? (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Sketch of Veterinary Medical Center, 2000? (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Aerial photos of Veterinary Complex about 1957; cars in crescent shaped parking lot., 1957 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - View of Schurman Hall and Small Animal Clinic, about 1957., 1957 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Aerial view of Veterinary Complex, about 1957; No cars in crescent shaped parking lot., 1957 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Folder of Schurman Hall building diagrams by floor and area., 1957 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - NYS College of Agriculture barns with large Elm tree on right, 1913? (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Dark colored gabled barn with 2 extensions; 2 round silos on left., 1913? (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Several dark colored barns, 1913 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - View over Libe Slope toward West Campus in spring (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Series VI. Calenders and Schedules
  - Activities Calendar, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Academic Calendars, 1979-1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Class Schedules, 1974-1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Exam Schedules, 1966-1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Clinic Assignments and Sections, 1962-1980 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Activities Calendar, 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Series VII. Committees and Boards
  - Standings Committees of the Faculty-List, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Advisory Council (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Task Force for Curriculum Review, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - The Cornell Veterinarian (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Centennial Sub-Committee - Commemorative Projects, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Centennial Committee, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Centennial Celebration, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Series VIII. Departments, Units, and Services
  - Anatomy Department (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Auto Tutorial Center, 1970's (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Auto Tutorial Center - Planning, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Avian and Aquatic Department (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Baker Institute (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Baker Institute - Conferences and Workshops (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Biomedical Communications, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Department of Clinical Sciences (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Clinical and Biomedical Science (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Diagnostic Laboratory (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Diagnostic Laboratory - Test and Fee Schedule, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Equine Clinic, etc., 1980s (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Equine Research Park, 1963-ca. 1970s (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Farriery, 1955, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Feline Health Center (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Feline Health Center - Louis J. Calmuti Memorial Feline Consultation and Diagnostic Service, 1977-1981, 1991, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Department of Histology and Embryology, 1900-1918 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Hospital (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Hospital-Animal Behavior Clinic (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Hospital/Clinics - Clinical Notes - Large Animal Surgery (8 volumes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
  - Hospital/Clinics - Clinical Notes - Small Animal Surgery (1 volume, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
  - Hospital/Clinics - Clinical Notes - Small Animal Medicine (3 volumes, 1896-1918 (Box 14)
  - Hospital/Clinics - Unidentified Large Animal Record Book, 1934-1941 (Box 14)
  - Laboratory Animal Diagnostic Resource, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Laboratory Animal Medicine (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Laboratory for Pregnancy and Newborn Research, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory of Veterinary Physiology and Pharmacology, 1904-1906 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Laboratory of Veterinary Physiology and Pharmacology, 1907-1910 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Large Animal Medicine,Obstetrics, and Surgery, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Annual Report on Reproductive Research
  - Large Animal Medicine, Obstetrics, and Surgery, 1940's (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Course Bibliographies
  - LAMOS-Student Surgery Papers-under Danks, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    1 of 3
  - LAMOS-Student Surgery Papers-under Danks, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    2 of 3
  - LAMOS-Student Surgery Papers-under Danks, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    3 of 3
  - LAMOS-Student Surgery Papers-under Delahanty, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    1 of 2
  - LAMOS-Student Surgery Papers-under Delahanty, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    2 of 2
  - Department of Medicine (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Microbiology, Immunology, and Parasitology (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Molecular Medicine (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Pathology (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Pathology - "Early post mortem notes before organization in 1917, and duplicates of later type-written noes", 1910-1920 (Box 20)
  - Physical Biology (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Physiology (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Zweig Memorial Fund for Equine Research (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Photographs and Slides
  - Ambulatory and Production Medicine - some slides, 1980s-2003 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Diagnostic Lab - slides, 1980s-2002 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Equine Hospital, no dates (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Farm Animal Hospital - some slides, 1980s-2000 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Series IX. Events and classes
  - Annual Conference (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Black Tie and Tails, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Black Tie and Tails, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Caliente y Frio: An Exhibit of Wildlife Art, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    By Fabian Martinez
  - Christmas Party (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Centennial-General, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Centennial Book-General, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Centennial-Book-Decade Summaries, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Centennial-Book-Department and Organization Summaries, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Centennial-Book-Notes from Faculty and Alumni (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Centennial-Book-Published Resources, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Centennial-Time Capsule, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Commencement and Hooding (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Commencement and Hooding-Programs (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Honor Day (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Honor Day-Prizes-H.H. Dukes Prize-General, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Honor Day-Prizes-H.H. Dukes Prize-Donor Letters, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Open House (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Reunions (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Semi-Centennial, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Event Flyers to Open House, Exhibitions, James Law Distinguished Lecture Series, Commencement, and Caliente y Frio (Box 9)
  - Governors Citations (Box 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1903,1907,1956,1960,1963 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1971,1973,1975,1978-1979 (Box 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1984-1985,1987,1991 (Box 9)
  - Maps and Sketches of campus and facilities (Box 9)
  - Poster in memory for Franklin M. Loew (Box 9)
  - Cartoon Sketch (Box 9)
  - Place Cards for Honor Day - Caricature of the Faculty, by Vincent Paciello, 1940 (Box 16)
  - Place Cards for Honor Day - Animals, by Rebecca Gifford, 1940 (Box 17)
  - Millennium Time Capsule, 2000 (Box 8)
  - Photographs and Slides
  - Reunions, 1990s-2001 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Reunions, 1945 and 1990s (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Reunions, Various Dates (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Reunion - Class of 1951, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Reunion - Class of 1951, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Reunion - Class of 1951, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Reunion - Class of 1996, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Reunions - Classes of 1946, 1971, 1981, 1986, 1996, 2001, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Centennial, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Centennial Room Dedication, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Commencement, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Equine Events - slides, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Events - Miscellaneous, 1980s-1990s (Box 34, Folder 10)